Here's to us, the Moonlit Black
Cats! Cheers, everyone! Cheers!
I got another!
Here's to the guy who saved
our lives, Takirito! Takirito!
Uh, cheers, guys. Thanks.
Yeah, man. Thank you.
You saved us back there.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
Uh, it's cool.
I can't tell you how scared I was,
and it made me so happy when
you came to save us, I...
Oh, well, uh, Kirito, sir?
I hope I'm not out of line asking this,
but I was wondering what level you're at.
Level 20?
Really?
You're at our level and
still a solo player?
You're an inspiration, sir! Cait,
I'm not your superior,
and being solo means I'm always
hunting enemies out in the boonies.
It's not very efficient.
Oh, right.
Well, in that case,
I hate to spring this on you here,
but if you want, we'd love
to have you in our guild.
Our mace wielder, Tetsuo, is the only
one we can put out front right now.
And then we've got Sachi over here.
I was thinking of having her
switch to sword and shield.
That way, she can fight
on the front lines.
The thing is, she says she's
not sure she can handle it.
If you join us, maybe you
could teach her a thing or two.
Oh, come on.
I'm not that useless.
Seriously, you can't just put me up
front and expect me to know what to do.
I'd be terrified.
It's no big deal.
Just hide behind your shield.
Yeah, right.
Ever since I can remember,
you've always been a Sigurd cat.
We always joke around like that.
See, in real life,
we all go to the same high school
and are members of the computer club.
But if you're worried about
fitting in with us, don't.
As far as I'm concerned, you're
already part of our group.
Right? Mm-hmm.
Well, I'm really flattered.
And thanks for the offer.
I'll do it.
I'm afraid of the back of my
back, but I can't believe it.
I've seen a few times in the sky.
Here it is, surely, a beautiful heart.
It's a dream.
I love you!
What do you think?
Your body is so good I'm not
even gonna give you a chance
I'm not even looking at you
I'm not looking at you I
can't believe in my dreams,
I want to always be waiting
I'll give you everything I have
Sachi! Get back! I got this!
Come on, Tetsuo! Switch out! Got it!
All right!
Congrats, man!
You totally owned that sucker!
The assault team made
it through to floor 28.
That's amazing!
Hey Kirito, what the heck does the
assault team have that we don't? Well,
access to information—with
that they can find out the
easiest ways to get XP—and
they don't share that info.
Yeah, you're probably
right, but I think what?
think what really sets
them apart is willpower.
What do you mean?
I guess what I mean is.
They have the will to
stick up for their friends.
or any player for that matter.
Truth is, I like to think we
have that same kind of drive,
even though we still
need their protection.
That said, our first priority
is looking out for each other.
But someday, if we get strong enough,
we'll join the elites in the assault team.
I see.
That's a good goal.
I don't know. I guess.
Hey, leader, give me some love!
So,
you really think we can
be as strong as the Holy
Dragon Alliance or the
Knights of the Blood Oath?
Yeah, what if I do?
Nothing wrong with setting our sights
high, but we have to be level 30 first.
That's impossible.
I like the way Cait thinks.
If the Black Cats can level up
fast and get to the front lines,
his ideals could change the elitist
attitude of the assault team.
I have an announcement to make.
After our latest hunts in the
field, we've got 200,000 coal.
Awesome!
Buying a house of our own doesn't
seem like such a pipe dream anymore.
I know!
We should upgrade Sachi's equipment.
Good idea.
I'm fine with what I have.
Oh, come on.
You know, it's not fair to make
Kirito be out in front forever.
I'm sorry.
Don't worry about me.
I'm cool with it.
Thanks, Kirito.
Sachi, I know switching jobs isn't easy,
but seriously, you're almost there!
You can do it, I know it!
Klein.
What's up, Kirito?
The trash mob's all yours, guys. Sure.
Man, it's been a while
since I've seen you.
What, you doing some late-night
leveling or something?
What's up with that icon?
Did you join a guild?
Yeah, I guess you could say that.
It's all clear!
We can move on!
See ya.
Yeah.
Oh, come on.
Is it still bugging you?
It's Cait.
Sachi went off somewhere
and hasn't come back yet.
We're heading to the dungeon now.
Please let me know if
you find anything out.
Sachi…
Sachi?
Kirito…
Everyone's worried about you.
Hey, Kirito. Yeah?
We should run away.
Run away?
From what?
From this town.
From the monsters.
From the moonlit black cats.
And from Sword Art Online, too.
Are you talking about suicide?
That's not such a bad idea.
Sorry, no.
If I had the guts to die, I wouldn't be
hiding in town where it's safe, would I?
But really, why can't we just leave?
Why do we have to die when
it's just a stupid game?
What's the point of going through this?
Yeah, there is no point, I guess.
i i'm so afraid of dying in here
it's really that bad for you
i'm so scared i haven't been
able to get any sleep lately
you're not going to die
really how can you be so
sure about that the black
cats are strong enough
as a guild.
Besides, our margin of safety
is well above the norm.
Plus, you got Tetsuo and me up front,
so there's no reason to be
on the frontlines with us.
You honestly don't think I'll die?
Will I make it back to the real world?
Yeah, you're not gonna die. You'll see.
We'll clear this game and go home soon.
Come in.
I'm sorry.
I can't seem to get to sleep.
If I stay in this guild,
she'll be safe, and we'll all make
it back to the real world someday.
There must be a lot of players like
her who are afraid of dying here.
But still, they laugh and cry
and try to live as best they can.
I never thought about it like that before.
Kirito?
It's okay.
I promise you're going to survive.
And no matter what, I promise
I'll protect all of you.
Okay, I'm heading out.
Teleport!
Town of Beginnings!
Can you believe it?
I never thought buying a
house would be so exciting!
Dude, you sound like an old man.
Hey,
while Kato's off buying the house,
what do you guys say we go
out and raise some extra cash?
Oh, then we can buy furniture!
Come on, let's go to a
dungeon on a higher floor!
We should stick to our
usual hunting spots.
But up there, we could
make more and faster.
Yeah, and at our levels, we don't
have anything to worry about.
You see?
I told you guys this was going to be cake.
We might even be able to
reach the front line sooner.
That's what I'm talking about. Look.
No way.
A hidden door?
A treasure chest! Woo-hoo!
No, wait!
It's a trap, guys!
Hurry!
Let's get out of here!
Teleport theft!
We can't use our crystals!
They're probably being
blocked by the walls
Yeah!
Stacia!
Kiriko!
I hear someone's been taking
risks with their level raising.
You got any new info for me or what?
Nothing worth charging you money for.
You give info brokers a bad name.
Hey, this wasn't in the beta test.
It's a first-time event.
How am I supposed to
know what's gonna happen?
All I know is that tonight on Christmas
Eve, the event boss is gonna appear.
He's called Nicholas the Renegade,
and he's gonna show up
under a fir tree somewhere.
The major guilds are searching
everywhere for the tree as we speak.
You wouldn't happen to know
where it is, would you?
Maybe.
Are you thinking of
going solo on this one?
In this world, the dead
can never return to life.
I heard a rumor, though.
If you beat Nicholas the Renegade, he'll
drop an item that can revive a dead player.
I'm going alone, and
I'll probably die alone.
No one will see me, no one will know.
Nothing will be left behind.
That's how I'll die.
You're a beater.
You had no right to be with us.
That's right.
It's my fault.
My arrogance killed you.
All of you.
If only I hadn't kept my true level
as a player secret from everyone.
I have to figure out a
way to beat Nicholas.
Then I can revive Sachi.
And then I'll find out what
she was trying to tell me.
And if it turns out she
was cursing me, fine.
I accept it.
What's up?
You followed me? Of course.
You're after the revival item, aren't you?
Yeah.
Don't be risking your life for some
rumor that could turn out to be bogus.
Man, you can't be messing
around in this death game.
Once your HP hits zero, that's it.
In the real world, your
brain gets fried and it's...
Shut up.
I'm trying to get you to stop
with all your stupid soloing.
Come on, join up with us.
Whoever gets it to drop
the revival item keeps it.
No hard feelings.
Hey, that's fair, isn't it?
But then, there'd be no point.
I have to do this. Alone.
Think about what you're doing, Kirito.
It's suicide, and I can't
let you die like that.
Come on!
I guess you were being followed,
too, huh, Klein? Uh-huh.
It sure looks that way.
It's the Holy Dragon Alliance.
They'll do anything for a rare
item, no matter how shady.
What do we do?
You bastards.
Screw these guys!
Get out of here, Kirito! No way.
Leave them to us.
We can hold them off.
Get going!
I don't know.
Let's do this.
Kirito, hey!
There, that's the revival item.
Let's see; it says: "must
administer to affected player
within 10 seconds." If someone dies in
front of you someday, make sure you use it!
Kirito! Listen.
Stay alive, you hear?
I don't care how you do it.
Just stay alive to the end.
See ya.
Saatchi…
Merry Christmas, Kirito.
By the time you hear this,
I'll probably be dead.
How can I explain this?
Let's see...
To tell you the truth, I never really
wanted to leave the town of beginnings.
And I knew if I fought with an attitude
like that, I would end up dying someday.
But that's not anyone's fault.
That's something I have to deal with.
Kirito, ever since that
night you found me,
you kept telling me I wasn't
going to die no matter what.
But what if I got killed anyway?
I knew that if I died,
you'd blame yourself.
That's why I decided
to record this for you.
By the way, I know how
powerful you really are. Sorry.
I sort of peaked when you weren't looking.
I wondered why you
weren't telling the truth
about what level player you really were.
I wondered why you
decided to fight with us.
I never figured it out, though.
You know what?
When I found out how strong you were,
I don't know, it made me so happy.
I felt relieved.
So even if I die, promise me
you'll go on living, okay, Kirito?
Stay alive, so you can see the end of this
world and find out why it was created.
Find out why a weakling
like me ended up here.
Find out the reason you and I met.
Please.
That's what I wish.
Looks like I still have time, so seeing
how it's Christmas and everything,
I'll sing you a song.
Anyway, Kirito, I'm so glad I met you.
And that I could be with
you, even for a little while.
Thank you, goodbye.
Let's go.
Next time, the Black Swordsman